Anthony Karlo Bantugan



anthonykarlo.bantugan@gmail.com



+639985691758



linkedin.com/in/anthony-karlo-bantugan-3059b0227

https://react-portfolio-sigma-six.vercel.app/

Summary

I am a JavaScript developer with a passion for making things that matter. I have been programming since 2021, and during my time in a Web Development bootcamp, I grew my skills to work on the frontend and backend using the MERN stack technologies. I am looking for opportunities where I can use my skills and creativity to create fun projects.

SKILLS:

React.js, Node.js, Express.js, JavaScript (ES6), Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Git, REST API, PHP, Laravel

Experience

№ Postgraduate Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022 (5 months)

- -Full stack web development with React.js and Express.js
- -Built a MERN stack Ecommerce app as the capstone project.

Demo: https://capstone-3-mu.vercel.app/

Administrative Assistant

RMCMA Beauty Service Center

Jan 2013 - Aug 2021 (8 years 8 months)

- Provides administrative support to ensure efficient operation of office.
- Answers phone calls, schedules meetings and supports visitors.
- Carries out administrative duties such as filing, typing, copying, binding, scanning etc.
- Supports team by performing tasks related to organization and strong communication.

Education

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Postgraduate Degree

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022

A web development bootcamp focusing on both frontend and backend technologies such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP, mySQL, Laravel, React.js, MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js



Ateneo de Davao University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Accounting Technology/Technician and Bookkeeping Jul 2008 - May 2012

Licenses & Certifications

Zuitt Coding Bootcamp Certificate of Completion - Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/b78f5bce-79df-402e-89a4-d2251cbd5a45/

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • JavaScript • Node.js • Git • MongoDB • React.js • PHP • SQL